
  
	//問題文を格納する要素です
	const quiz = [
	  {
		question: "After several months of _____ , Russo Corporation has decided to move its headquarters to Los Angeles.",
		answers: ["considered", "considers", "considering", "consideration"],
		correct: "consideration"
	  },
	  {
		question: "In _____ one year, our company became the second largest company in the suimsuit industory.",
		answers: ["recently", "alone", "just", "thoroughly"],
		correct: "just"
	  },
	  {
		question: "XTZ Corporation, a _____ manufacturer of mobile phones, plans to merge with Axxion Communications.",
		answers: ["leads", "leader" ,"leading", "leadership"],
		correct: "leading"
	  },
	  {
		question: "Due to the opening of our overseas outlets, sales are expected to increase by _____ ten percent next year.",
		answers: ["approximate", "approximation", "approximately", "approximates"],
		correct: "approximately"
	  },
	  {
		question: "The research results indicate _____ parents with small children tend to purchase more organic produce.",
		answers: ["much", "about", "that", "to"],
		correct: "that"
	  },
	  {
		question: "Sunpool Appliances has released a new sewing machine _____ a programmable control system with a touch-screen interface.",
		answers: ["feature", "featuring", "features", "featured"],
		correct: "featuring"
      },
	  {
		question: "The manager had the staff members come to the conference room five minutes early _____ the meeting could start on time.",
		answers: ["because", "as soon as", "while", "so that"],
		correct: "so that"
	  },
	  {
		question: "We are _____ to announce that Mr.Allen Archer of the accounting department has been promoted to vice president.",
		answers: ["pleasant", "pleasing", "pleased", "pleasure"],
		correct: "pleased"
	  },
	  {
		question: "Analysts are _____ that a decline in consumer spending could threaten the nation's economic recovery.",
		answers: ["instructing", "predicting", "reviewing", "watching"],
		correct: "predicting"
	  },
	  {
		question: "The customer service department has frequentry received questions _____ pollution and the environment.",
		answers: ["regard", "regarding", "regards", "regarded"],
		correct: "regarding"
	  },
	  {
		question: "If the shopkeeper had not offered a discount, Shelly _____ the jacket yesterday.",
		answers: ["will not by", "will not have bought", "would not buy", "would not have bought"],
		correct: "would not have bought"
	  },
	  {
		question: "Ms. Towne is a well regarded internet expert, having _____ numerous Web sites for a diverse array of clients.",
		answers: ["design", "designs", "designer", "designed"],
		correct: "designed"
	  },
	  {
		question: "Manhattan is a place _____ many restaurants serve customers at all hours of the day or night.",
		answers: ["that", "where", "which", "who"],
		correct: "where"
	  },
	  {
		question: "Mr.Hearn asked his secretary to bring _____ copy of the report to the conference room.",
		answers: ["another", "each other", "other", "one another"],
		correct: "another"
	  }
	];
  
